干脆给他耳朵后面来一枪  毙了算了
I say we pop him. One right behind the ear.
这样太便宜他了
That's too good for him.
姑娘们还好吗
You girls all right?
还好
Yeah.
给你  我们捡了这个
Here. We picked that up.
或许能从这上面查到什么
There might be something on it.
无论如何  动作要快
Whatever you do, do it quick.
英国大兵落到爱尔兰共和军手里
We all know what happens to British soldiers
下场会怎样  我们都很清楚
in the hands of the IRA, don't we?
有情报吗  有袭击方面的邮件吗
Picked up any chatter? Any e-mails about this attack?
升级了  但没有什么特别的地方
Levels are up, but nothing specific.
卡马里呢
What about Kamali?
随时可能会到
Should be here any minute.
那我们就以目前所掌握的情报开始工作
All right, let's work with what we have.
我们有欧瑞沃登上周的行踪
We have O'Riordan's movements over the last week.
还有机场的监控录像
We have CCTV footage from the airport.
在袭击开始前  我们最多只有一天时间了
We have 24 hours--tops-- before this attack.
趴在地上
On the ground.
我只是...
I Just...
我想这里应该没有地方让我梳洗一番吧
I don't suppose you've got somewhere I could freshen up?
看来是真没有
I take it that's a "No," Then.
够了
Enough.
起来
Get up.
挖
Dig.
你都掌握我儿子哪些信息
What do you know about my son?
我哥哥就是这么死的
This is how my brother died.
脑后中了一枪
Bullet in the back of the head.
被埋在自掘的坟墓里
Buried in a grave he dug himself.
布达佩斯  英国大使馆
你查到什么了吗
You got anything?
稍等
One a second.
就在袭击前不到一小时
Phone call made from the airport
机场那边来过一通电话
less than an hour before the attack.
电话打给谁的
To who?
穆赫塔尔·穆萨维
Moukhtar Mousawi,
这里黎巴嫩人圈子里的杰出的商人
a prominent businessman in the Lebanese community here.
在十三区经营着一家汽车专卖行
Runs the car dealership in District 13.
-注意  -李奥
- Heads up.  - Leo.
我尽快赶了过来
I came as soon as I could.
谢谢你能过来  艾斯特怎么样
Thanks for coming. How's Ester?
安全
Safe.
你认识这个人吗
You know that guy?
穆赫塔尔·穆萨维
Moukhtar Mousawi.
他是朱海瑞在欧洲的帮手之一
He's one of al-Zuhari's fixers in Europe.
-好的  -他们带走了洛克
- Right.  - They took Locke.
那么穆赫塔尔·穆萨维一定知道洛克关在哪里
Then Moukhtar Mousawi will know where they're holding him.
那么要想有进展  我们只能倚靠他了
Which makes him our only solid lead to the attack.
这样做很冒险  不过我可以跟他谈谈
It's risky, but I could talk to him.
聊天时间结束
Mm-mm. Time for talk is over.
阿迈  我们走
Mikey, let's go.
瑞姆  你把地址给我们
Richmond, you get us that address?
没问题
Yup.
你相信梦吗
You believe in dreams?
信
Yes.
都拿着吧
Keep it.
我做了个噩梦
I had a bad dream.
你最近在贝鲁特丢的东西
The things you lost on your recent holiday in Beirut
有人找到了
have been found.
你还好吗
You all right?
还好
Yeah.
你为什么会这么问
Why wouldn't I be?
你不是有几枪没打中嘛
Those couple of shots you missed.
只是随便问问
Just asking.
我到大使馆的医生那儿检查过了
Yeah. I checked in with the embassy doctor.
她正在进行一些测试
She's running some tests.
很好
That's good.
你认为有可能是什么
What do you think it could be?
精神上的还是身体上的
Mental? Physical?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以前的同事也出现过类似情况
I've seen it on guys I came up with.
身体还算健康  但是...
Physically, you're fine, but...
精神上就没那么幸运了
mentally...no.
事业达到了巅峰状态
You've reached the top of your game
而压力和情感也随之被推到了极限
and the pressure and the emotional cost,
只是...
it just...
这样就离走下坡路不远了
It's not long before it starts to slip away, you know?
你没有什么好担心的
You got nothing to worry about.
多谢了  搭档
Well, cheers, mate.
你离事业巅峰还早得很呢
You're nowhere near the top of your game.
你个死鬼
You fucking asshole.
因为这些事  你开始想那些钻石了吗
Is that what's making you think about these diamonds?
也许吧
Maybe.
但若你不洗手退出的话 总有被抓的一天
But you don't get out, you get got, right?
明白
Copy that.
听过一个故事没
Did you ever hear the one
是关于英国人  爱尔兰人和阿拉伯人的
about the Englishman and the Irishman and the Arab?
没有吗  冷酷的人们
Yeah? Tough crowd.
不要这样
Don't do this.
待在原地不许动
Stay where the fuck you are.
这是我们之间的恩怨
This is between you and me.
我很喜欢你哥哥
I liked your brother.
你喜欢弗兰西
You liked Francie?
你他妈的改变了他  陷害了他
You fucking turned him. Set him up.
让他背叛自己所爱的人  你就是恶源
Made him betray the people he loved. The cause.
那是一场肮脏的战争  马芮
It was a dirty war, Mairead.
我那晚是要去警告他
That night, I went to warn him.
你是为了保护该死的线人
To protect your fucking source.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
为什么把他带到这儿来
Why did you even bring him here?
这与你无关
This has nothing to do with you.
听见了吗  退后
You heard her. Fuck off.
放下枪
我们还需要这些狗腿子
若你们想让朱海瑞兑现承诺
If you want what al-Zuhari has promised,
我们就得搞清他知道些什么
we should find out what he knows.
去他的
Fuck it.
他对于我毫无用处
He's nothing to me.
你们计划攻击北约
You guys are planning to attack NATO,
最好还是团结点
you better get your act together.
他什么都不知道
He knows nothing.
他是想耍我们
He's trying to play us.
那我们得确认一下
We have to be sure.
-我讨厌等待  -是啊
- Fuck. I hate waiting.  - Yeah.
洛克有个孩子  是吗
So, Locke had a kid, huh?
是的  特种空勤团在北爱尔兰采取的手段很强硬
He did. The SAS played hardball in Northern Ireland,
-这个你知道对吧  -知道
- as you know. - Yeah.
爱尔兰共和军杀了他儿子
The IRA killed Locke's son.
-靠  -是够操蛋的
- Fuck. - Yeah.
你早知道了
And you knew?
嗯  是的
Yeah, I suppose I did.
人人都有不想谈及之事  是吧兄弟
But we all have things we don't talk about, right, mate?
的确如此
Yes, we do.
穆萨维出现了
There's Mousawi.
我看起来怎么样
How do I look?
像极了暴发户
Like a man who has more money than taste.
很好  要的就是这个效果
That's good. That's exactly what I was going for.
那就是这样
Well, it works.
皮质的...
Leather...
而且四个胎全有
and it has all the 4 tires.
看  四个全有
There. Is all 4.
女士  你喜欢这款吗
You like, Mother? This?
喜欢这个颜色吗
Like the color?
会说英语吗
Speak English?
这辆车是个尤物
Ah. The car. Is a beautiful thing.
没错
It is.
穆赫塔尔·穆萨维
Moukhtar Mousawi.
格兰特·霍金斯
Grant Hawkins.
我喜欢美国人
I love Americans.
我也是
So do I.
有很多关于车的歌曲
So many songs about cars.
布鲁斯·斯普林斯汀的《卡迪拉克庄园》
Bruce Springsteen, "Cadillac Ranch."
珍妮丝·贾普林的《梅赛德斯·奔驰》
Janis Joplin, "Mercedes Benz."
没错  道路也能很浪漫
Yep. Romance of the road.
霍金斯先生  你为什么来匈牙利
What brings you to Hungary, Mr. Hawkins?
因为未婚妻
Fiancee.
你要结婚了
You're getting married?
是啊  三婚了
Yeah. Third time lucky.
美国佬  比阿拉伯人老婆还多的也就属你们了
Americans-- the only people with more wives than Arabs.
是啊  但我们得一个一个来
Yeah, but we only get one at a time.
除了犹他州
Except in Utah.
没错
That's true.
你很风趣  穆赫塔尔
You're a funny man, Moukhtar.
-我能试驾一下吗  -请便
- May I? - Please. Be my guest.
谢谢
Thank you.
实话实说  朋友
Let me tell you, my friend,
这会是你开过最安全的车了
this is one of the safest cars you could drive.
为什么这么说
Heh. Why is that?
因为是金属车身吗
Because it's made of metal?
你有孩子吗
Ha ha! You have children?
我和未婚妻正考虑呢
Me and my fiancee are thinking about it,
但我自己还有点孩子气
but I'm still a bit of a kid myself.
你想试驾吗
You would like to take it for a test drive?
我可以安排一名销售
I could arrange for one of my sales--
不用管我  伙计
Don't mind me, mate.
你自便
You'll do.
搞什么
What--
什么情况
What's going on?
据贝鲁特一个叫格雷的人透露
We were tipped off by a man called Gray in Beirut
有人想要北约的情报
that somebody was after NATO intel.
每个基地和设施
Every single base and installation
都已全面戒备
is on full alert.
那北约的网络中枢呢
And the NATO hub?
你他妈还要泄露多少信息给他
Anything else you want to fucking tell him?
他反正都要死
He'll die here.
那么你们想要什么
So, what is it you're after?
后勤数据  基地运行细节吗
Logistics data? Base operational details?
很可惜  你们不走运
Well, sadly, you're out of luck.
访问协议我已经下命令
The access protocols have been changed...
更改了
on my orders.
新的协议是什么
What is the new protocol?
就目前的形式来看  我没必要说吧
From where I'm standing, that's hardly an incentive, is it?
没错
You're right.
等等
Wait.
我有更好的办法
I know a better way.
我本想在抠扳机之前
I was going to save this
才告诉你的
till the moment before I pulled the trigger.
我知道谁杀了你儿子
I know who killed your son.
告诉我们新的协议
Give us the protocol
我就告诉你名字
and I'll give you the name.
让我开门  我想开门
Let me open it. I want to open it.
给我钥匙
Give me the keys.
-谢谢爸爸  -到了告诉我
- Thanks, Dad.  - Let me know when you get there.
我是洛克
Locke.
你哪位
Who is this?
为了赎你的罪  菲利普...
For your sins, Philip...
你想怎样
What do you want?
补偿
Payback.
安东尼
Anthony!
好吧
Yeah.
二十年了  伤口依旧很疼吧
20 years and it still hurts, doesn't it?
看来你还算是个人
You must be human after all.
幸好你妻子还活着
At least your wife survived. Lucky.
她会得到你的抚恤金的
She'll get to pick up your pension.
我觉得用幸存这个词更好
I suppose you could call it surviving.
四肢瘫痪  坐着轮椅
In a wheelchair, quadriplegic,
全身六成烧伤
60% burns.
你们称之什么来着  间接伤害
What do you boys call it? Collateral damage?
你知道是谁安装的炸弹
You know who planted the bomb?
和制作者是同一人
The same man as built it.
只有另一个炸弹具有相同的特征
There was only one other device with the same signature.
96年金丝雀码头爆炸案
Canary Wharf. 96.
1996年2月9日  爱尔兰共和军对伦敦金丝雀码头发动的恐怖袭击事件
我能告诉你上哪找他
I could point you straight at him.
你无论如何都会杀了我
You're going to kill me anyway.
那你还想知道吗
You still want to know?
他死全是因为你的身份...
He died because of who you are...
你所做的一切
what you did.
每当我闭上眼睛  我不仅能看到他
You know, when I close my eyes, I don't just see my boy.
还能感觉到他在我脖子上留下的气息
I feel his breath on my neck.
能感觉到他曾经的体温
I feel the warmth he used to give me.
我曾想给每一个涉及其中
There was a time I would've put a bullet
参与杀害我儿子的混蛋都开上一枪  但是...
into every bastard that helped kill him, but...
安东尼已死  弗兰西已逝
Anthony's dead. Francie's dead.
你活在过往之中  马芮
You're living in the past, Mairead.
那场战争结束了
That war's done.
你不会真的相信结束了吧
You don't really believe that, do you?
你们这是绑架
This is kidnapping!
你也好意思提"绑架"
It's funny you mention kidnapping.
你知道菲利普·洛克这名字吗
You know the name Philip Locke? Huh?
不错  刹车还能用
There we go. Brake works.
你觉得这车还有其他安全装置吗
You think there's any other safety features on this car?
不清楚啊  再试试吧
I don't know. Let's find out.
就试试呗
Let's do that.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
就目前来说  我们在倒车
At the moment, looks like we're going backwards.
快刹车
All right, brakes!
这类老式车装有安全气囊吗  阿迈
These models got passenger airbags, Mikey?
我觉得只有一个办法来搞清楚了  哥们
I think there's only one way to find out, mate.
我也这么觉得
Mm. Me, too.
别  别  等会
No, no. Wait.
不  等会  停  停  停车
No, wait, wait, stop, stop, stop!
现在停不下来了
I can't stop now!
刚才够惊险的  对吧
Boy, that was a clincher, wasn't it?
等着呢
Waiting.
-好吧  -等等  等会
- All right. - Wait, wait, wait.
要是朱海瑞知道是我...
If al-Zuhari finds out...
我不会告诉他的  阿迈呢
I'm not gonna tell him. Mikey?
绝对保密  哥们
Mum's the word, mate.
听到了吧  他不会知道的
There you go. So, he's not gonna find out.
怎么不说话呢  快点
Cat got your tongue? Come on.
九号区一间废弃的工厂
An abandoned factory. District 9.
我操
Fuck.
-你没事吧  -你能看到枪手位置吗
- You all right? - You see where it's coming from, mate?
是啊  让我探出脑袋去望望
Oh, yeah, let me stick my head up and take a look, mate.
-没动静  操你妈的破引擎  -操
- Nothing. Nothing! Fucking engine. -Shit.
该死的
Fuck.
给你
Here.
就拿这个砸他  真他妈的好主意
Oh, fucking throw that at him great idea.
丢给你的
Throw it at you.
操你祖宗大爷的
Fuck. Fuck.
该死的  高点  迈克  再高点
Fuck. Goddamn. Up, Mike. Up.
我操
Fuck.
-看到枪手了吗  -他下车了
- You see him? - He's jumping out.
他正走过来  阿迈
Here he comes, Mikey.
他朝我们走过来了
He's coming toward us.
等他换弹夹...
As soon as he changes...
行动
Go.
你觉得他是爱尔兰共和军的人吗
Uhh. You think he's IRA?
他是沃瑞的人
He's Vory.
那是什么狗屁  听起来像个邪恶精灵
What the fuck is that? Sounds like an evil elf.
沃瑞·维·扎孔尼  俄罗斯黑手党
Vory v Zakone. Russian Mob.
英文字面意思为"守法窃贼"
看到这些纹身了吗
You see these tattoos?
它们就像简历
They're like a CV.
可以看出这个人除了名字之外的所有经历
They tell you everything except his name.
你他妈怎么知道这些狗屁的
How the fuck do you know all that shit?
这家伙是个杀手
And this one, he's an assassin.
-看出来了  迈克  -是吗
- I got that, Mike. - Yeah?
当然
Yeah.
就是这人
That's the man.
那个沃瑞杀手肯定就是阿卡帝·乌尔诺夫派出的
Arkady Ulyanov almost certainly sent the Vory to kill you.
因为我们在哥伦比亚杀了他儿子
Because we killed his son in Colombia.
得了吧  被我们杀的人多了去了
Come on. We've killed heaps of dudes.
他们都是某人的儿子
They've all been someone's son.
为什么偏偏这人要 惹事生非呢
What makes that guy such a badass?
因为他是全俄罗斯最凶残黑帮的老大
Because he's the head of the most fierce mafia gang in Russia.
他手头上的资源顶得上一个小国家
He has the resources of a small country.
他也非常爱他的儿子
And he loved his son.
那你完蛋了
You're fucked then.
我完蛋  我完蛋  为什么是我完蛋
I'm fucked? I'm fucked? Why am I fucked?
你先开枪杀他的
You shot him first.
你也朝他开枪了
You shot him as well.
对  但我只是为了确保他已经死了
Yeah, but I only shot him to make sure he was dead.
你先朝他开枪的  那么所有邪恶精林门
You shot him first, so, all the evil elfs
都会去找你算账的
are gonna come after your ass.
是"精灵们"  不是"精林门"
It's "Elves," Not "Elfs."
英文中"Elf"的复数词应为"Elves"
有头绪了吗
You got anything?
有两间被废弃的工厂符合穆萨维的描述
Yeah. Two abandoned factories that fit with what Mousawi told us.
-能放大看吗  -大屏幕
- It's going up? - Big screen.
就这个吗
That's it?
那就是机场那辆装甲车
Well, that's the armored car from the airport.
就那了  行动
That's it. Let's move.
今天就是纪念日
Today is the anniversary.
今天就是朱海瑞在录像里说的圣日
Today is the holy day al-Zuhari referred to on the tape.
袭击可能在任何时间任何地点发动
The attack could happen anywhere, any moment.
我们出发
Let's go.
大家都小心点
Heads up, bud.
他什么也不会告诉你的
You'll get nothing from him.
一枪毙了就完了
Just shoot the fucker.
子弹和坟墓对我们毫无意义
A bullet and a shallow grave buy us nothing.
他还有些宣传价值
He has propaganda value.
随便你吧
Suit yourself.
以前你们参军是只为了看看世界
Used to be a time you joined the army to see the world, eh?
如今你已然成为虐杀电影里的主角
Now you get to star in your own snuff movie instead.
也算是进步了
I guess that's progress.
你何不告诉你朋友们
Why don't you tell your friends
弗兰西·麦坎娜到底是什么样的人  马芮
who Francie MacKenna really was, Mairead?
告诉大家他是为...
That he worked--
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut your filthy mouth.
你拍完后
When you're done,
记得发一份给他那苟延残喘的老婆看看
be sure to send a copy of the video to what's left of his wife.
走吧  是时候行动了
Come on. It's time.
在你两点钟方向就位
In position on your two.
阿迈  快上
Mikey, go.
操
Fuck.
斯科特  斯顿布奇
Scott! Stonebridge!
他们来啦
They're here.
现在谁都进不来  朋友
Nobody's going to enter now, my friend.
看着摄像机  看着摄像机  看好
Look at the camera. Look at the camera. Look!
跟着我重复  跟着我说
Say after me. Say after me.
-抱歉  我不懂  -跟着我重复
- Sorry, I didn't quite-- - Say after me!
我会杀了他的
I'll kill him!
开枪  斯科特
Shoot him, Scott.
开枪
Take the shot.
不行
I can't.
开枪
Take the shot.
不行  长官  毫无角度
I can't, boss. I got no shot.
快动手
Do it!
操
Fuck!
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
宝刀未老啊  阿迈
Still got it, Mikey.
真的吗
Really?
你还好吗  长官
You all right, boss?
中士
Sergeant.
都没事吧  没事吧
Good? Good?
没事
Yeah.
她的团伙正在行动  有三辆货车
Her crew's on the loose with 3 vans.
车里可能装满了塑胶炸药
They might be packed full of Semtex.
目标是什么
What are their targets?
不清楚  但肯定是今天行动
No idea, but it's happening today.
他们在想尽办法骇入北约的网络中枢
They're looking to crack the NATO hub somehow.
打给科维
Get hold of Covee.
立即更改访问协议
Make sure the protocols are changed immediately.
遵命
Sir.
谢谢你
Uhh. Thank you.
再找出100英里范围内
Then get me the location of every access point
所有接入点的位置
within 100 miles of here.
北约网络中枢是什么
What's the NATO hub?
是一个可以获取所有盟军情报的网关
It's the gateway to all allied intelligence.
我们要假设他们会将
We have to assume they're gonna download intel
一个或多个攻击目标的情报下载下来
on the target or targets they intend to attack.
格瑞说对了  道尔顿也对了
Gray was right. Dalton was right.
他们的目标是北约基地之一
They're targeting a NATO base.
帕波空军基地是北约在匈牙利的主要基地吗
Papa airbase is the main NATO base in Hungary, yeah?
-是的  -告诉他们有一级威胁
- Yeah. - Well, tell them we have a Code One level threat.
迫在眉睫
Imminent.
准备好了吗
Are we set?
保持头脑清醒
Keep your wits about you.
等等  那是其中一辆货车
Hold on. That's one of the vans.
在什么位置
Where is it?
约瑟夫广场  距此处仅一个街区
Josef Square. A block from here.
行动  疏散大楼里的人
Move. Evacuate the building.
-遵命  -收到
- Boss. - Sir.
-他们的目标一定是大使馆  -该死
- They have to be targeting the embassy. - Fuck.
通知当地政府
And alert the authorities.
还有两辆货车
There's two more vans.
东欧货车  都是绿色的
Eastern European. Both green.
一个浅绿  另一个深绿
One light, one dark.
为什么会是大使馆
Why the embassy?
长官  科维在前往停尸房的路上
Sir? Covee's on his way to the morgue.
他的助理纳塔丽今早发现身亡
His assistant Natalie was found dead this morning.
这绝不是巧合
That can't be a coincidence.
马上接通科维的电话
Get hold of Covee now.
长官
Sir.
那是一门可移式迫击炮
It's a mobile mortar rig.
拿下它
Secure it.
麦坎娜和一名同伙在现场
MacKenna's at the scene with another hostile.
收到
Copy that.
-迈克  迈克  -妈的他们来了
- Mike, Mike. - Here they fucking come!
-交火  - 操
- Contact! - Fuck!
-阿迈  -向你靠近
- Mikey. - Coming to you.
其他的货车
The other vans.
他们构成三角来包围大使馆
They're triangulating the embassy.
行动
Move!
向前移动
Moving!
炮弹发射了  掩护
Incoming! Cover!
你  快走  快走
You. Get out. Go. Move.
操
Fuck.
B组  我看到其它两辆货车了
Bravo team, I have the other two vans.
一辆在利奥波德公园
One at Leopold Park,
另一辆在斯图汉纳意桥
one at Sczechenyi Bridge.
中士  马上离开  这是命令
Sergeant, leave. Now. That's an order.
-迈克  -我在这
- Mike! - I'm here!
我去公园  你去那个桥
I'll run for the park! You go for the bridge!
收到  快走  快走
Yeah, roger that. Come on, come on.
我们走
Let's go.
李奥  自己找一个安全的地方待着
Leo, find somewhere safe and you stay there.
他妈的  立马接通科维的电话
For fuck's sake, put Covee on now!
操
Fuck.
解决一个
That's one down.
真爽啊
Fuck. Man.
空军上校  我是20号分部的瑞姆中士
Group Captain, this is Sergeant Richmond, Section 20.
麦坎娜的同伙在攻击大使馆
MacKenna's people are attacking the embassy.
-我们没有...  -听着
- We do not have-- - Listen.
所有经帕波空军基地
I have oversight of all NATO troops
前往阿富汗的北约军队都归我的监管
transiting through Papa airbase to Afghanistan.
他们为了得到通行卡而杀了我的助理
They killed my assistant to get her access card.
迈克
Mike!
不
No!
迈克  不
Mike, no!
总部  炮弹正朝你们而去  操
Zero, you have mortars inbound! Fuck!
不
No!
有没有人来帮忙
Can we get some help here?
快救他
Help this man.
英国大使馆
朱莉娅
Julia?
快找一个医护兵来  快
Get me a medic in here now. Now!
收到
Yeah, roger that.
打扰了  喂  打扰一下
Excuse me. Oi. Excuse me.
抱歉  我需要你的帮忙  跟我来
Excuse me. I need your help. Come here.
你会说英语吗  英语
Do you speak English? English?
过来  跟我来
Come here. Follow me.
上楼上楼  这边
Upstairs. Upstairs. Come here.
谁能过来帮一下忙
Can somebody give me a hand in here?
来了  我在这儿   长官
Yeah, I'm right here, boss.
过来这边  进来
Come here. Come here. Get in here.
朱莉娅
Julia.
别动  你会没事的
Stay still. You're gonna be OK.
朱莉娅  没事了  没事了
Julia, it's all right. It's all right.
别动  别动
Stay still. Stay still.
发生什么事了
What happened?
别担心  我们会处理好的
You don't have to worry about that. We're gonna take care of it.
在大使馆的禁区内
There's a NATO hub access point
有一台北约网络中枢的接入点
in the secure part of the embassy.
那不可能
That's impossible.
有的话  他们应该会告诉我们的
They would've briefed us on it.
只有顶级上司知道  科维知道
For Alpha Eyes Only. Covee.
他的权限远高于标准权限
He has much higher clearance than is standard.
在哪儿
Where is it?
-地下室  -地下室
- Basement. - Basement.
我想咱俩算是扯平了
I guess that's you and me even.
我们这儿有伤员吗
We've had casualties down here?
有收到求助信息
We get message.
纳塔丽·费希尔
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
医务人员是共和军的人扮的
Paramedics' IRA.
-她还好吧  -是  是的
- She all right? - Yeah, yeah.
她还活着
She's alive.
地下室有个接入点
There's an access point in the basement.
我们得马上下去  快点儿
We need to get there right now. Come on.
这儿有我  你们去吧
I've got this. You go.
她要是拿到访问权  我们就完了
She gains access, we're fucked.
该死
Shit.
你们怎么下来的
How did you get down here?
新的访问协议是什么
New access protocol.
我们没时间逞英雄了
We've no time for fucking heroes.
要是他们改了访问协议  怎么...
If they've changed the access protocol, how--
英国佬骗了我们三百年了
The Brits been lying to us for 300 years.
洛克在说谎
Locke was lying.
站住  阿迈
Stop! Mikey!
喂  站住
Oi! Stop.
-是他吗  -抱歉  抱歉
- Is that him? - Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-不是  -他妈的
- No. - Shit.
走  快走
Move. Move.
妈的快点儿  马芮  怎么这么久
C'mon to fuck, Mairead. What's taking so long?
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
我们已经尽力了
We've done our bit.
走
Move.
该死的  他们来了
Shit. Here they fucking come.
成功了
It's done.
操  快点  他们肯定抓住布莱登了
Fuck. Come on. They must have got Brendan.
什么
What--
妈的  操
Shit. Fuck.
走  拿着它
Go. Take it.
快走  在我改变主意前快滚
Go on. Fuck off before I change my mind.
换做弗兰西也会这么做的  不是吗
I'm only doing what Francie would've done, right?
你比他伟大多了
You're a better man than he ever was.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你们这帮该死的总是没完没了
You fuckers never know when to stop.
操  手榴弹  快躲
Fuck! Grenade! Move!
他妈的
Fuck!
你本该死了的
You should be dead.
你也差不多了
You're not far off yourself.
为了什么
And for what?
换来足够的自动步枪  炸药和导弹
Enough AK, Semtex, and Stingers
把你们永远赶出爱尔兰
to get your lot out of Ireland forever.
你真的觉得朱海瑞会履行承诺吗  马芮
Do you really think al-Zuhari will come good on that, Mairead?
英国佬居然还敢说阿拉伯人是混蛋
Listen to the Brit call the Arab a shifty bastard.
你们留在那儿
You stay there.
告诉我那个安放炸弹人的名字
Give me the name of the bomber,
那个杀了我儿子的人
the man who killed my son,
我向你保证  马芮
and I promise you, Mairead,
我会尽力帮助你的
I will do everything I can for you.
你说服了一个麦坎娜叛变
You turned one MacKenna.
但绝不会有另一个
You'll not turn another.
告诉我名字  我就保守弗兰西的秘密
You tell me and Francie's secret is safe.
你觉得为什么我会留下来
Why do you think I stayed?
而让博瑞格走了
Let Paidraig go?
一旦我死了  你就没公开的理由了
Once I'm dead, you've no reason to tell anyone.
无论怎样我都会做的
I'll do it anyway.
不  你不会
No. You won't.
因为你喜欢我哥哥的为人
Because you did like my brother.
阿迈  这儿交给你了
Mikey. You got this?
-行  -我去找个朋友
- Yeah. - I'm gonna go for a friend.
好的  收到
Yeah. Roger that.
人人都爱弗兰西
Everyone fucking loved Francie.
搞什么啊
What the fuck?
告诉我是谁杀了我儿子
The name of the man who killed my son.
哦  该死  上校
Oh, shit. Colonel.
我能搞定
I have this.
名字
The name.
看  战争对你来说也还没结束  是吧
See, the old war is not done for you yet, either, is it?
可怜的玩具兵
Poor, little toy soldier.
除了名字我还能提供更多
I can do better than a name.
让你和那个
How'd you like to speak to the man
杀了小安东尼的人通话如何
who killed your wee Anthony?
什么
What?
用我的手机
My phone.
-长官  -没事的
- Boss. - It's fine.
这是你我之间的事
This is between you and me.
不
No!
-出来  -她打算向你开枪
- Come here. - She was gonna shoot you!
卡马里  过来
Kamali! Come here.
枪  放下  放下
The gun. Put it down. Put it down.
-放下  -她打算向你开枪
- Put it down. - She was gonna shoot you.
妈的
Shit.
贱人
Bitch.
过来吧  来吧
Come here. Come on.
我们这儿还有止痛药吗
Do we have any more painkillers?
好的  给朱莉娅吗
Yeah. For Julia?
对  吗啡药效过去之后她会很疼
Yeah. She'll be sore when the morphine wears off.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Cheers.
现在可以谈谈晚餐的事了吗
Is now the time to talk about dinner?
那个  马丁内斯  我...
Um...look, Martinez, I'm...
我很荣幸  真的
I'm flattered. I really am.
不不  没关系
No, no. It's cool.
-哈哈  -怎么
- Ha! - Yup.
抱歉打断你们
Sorry to interrupt.
好吧  又开始了
Yup. Here we go.
你需要拿什么东西吗  斯科特中士
Is there something I can get for you, Sergeant Scott?
不  没关系  我去另一辆车拿
No, it's all good. I'll get it from the other one.
好  谢谢
OK. Thank you.
你看上去挺忙的  特别探员
Look like you got your hands full there, Special Agent.
斯科特  我们只不过是...
Here we go. Scott, it's just--
我懂得  伙计
I know what it is, dude.
-给瑞姆拿药  -没关系
- for Richmond-- All good.
-真的  -信你才怪
- Yup. - Uh-huh.
-你够了  -温柔点
- OK. - Be gentle.
好了  说够了吧
Yup. Good talk.
你憋了挺久了
Been a long time.
很好  非常好
Great. That's good.
他口风还算紧吧
He's not the talking type, right?
不  达米恩  他是谨慎的化身
Oh, no. Damien, he is the soul of discretion.
他...
He's--
-斯科特  -在
- Hey, Scott. - Yeah.
麦坎娜最后一个手下去哪儿了
What about the last of MacKenna's men?
不知道  逃走了
I don't know. He got away.
警察正在搜查
Cops are on.
我来接着她
I'm gonna grab her.
打起精神  到这来
Come on. Come here.
真是一团糟
What a mess.
你还好吗  中士
You all right, Sergeant?
是  长官
Yes, sir.
如果有问题你会告诉我的  对吗
You'd tell me if you weren't, wouldn't you?
当然
Yeah, of course.
你和医生谈过了
You spoke to the doctor?
对  她正在做一些化验
Yeah, she's running some tests.
常规体检  我要求的
Routine checkup, at my request.
她告诉我了
She said.
你还有什么想告诉我的吗
Anything else you want to tell me?
没有  长官  一切正常
No, sir. It's all good.
你和斯科特是我们的精英  迈克尔
You and Scott are at the tip of the spear, Michael.
这不是轻松活儿
It's not easy.
我懂  我是过来人
I know. I was that soldier.
是的  我理解
Yeah, I understand.
我和麦坎娜之前发生的事
And what happened between me and MacKenna...
都是过往历史了
was ancient history.
你也失去了家人
You lost family as well.
是的
Eh.
伤痛永远也忘不掉  是吗长官
It never goes away, does it, sir?
杀了汉森有帮助吗
Did it help? Killing Hanson?
我宽恕了他
I forgave him.
我问的不是这个
That's not what I asked.
说吧  你可以告诉我
Go on. You can tell me.
麦坎娜已经死了
MacKenna's dead.
我再也找不到那个混蛋了
I'll never find the bastard.
是的  有点帮助
Yeah. Yeah, it helped.
这正是我所害怕的
That's what I was afraid of.
你是个优秀的士兵  迈克尔
You're a good soldier, Michael.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
下一次我命令你射击时
The next time I tell you to take the shot,
你就射击
you take the shot.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
怎么样
So?
这真是...极其优异的品质
This is-- ahem--exceptional quality.
你从哪儿得到的
Where did you get it?
私人供货商
Private supplier.
你知道这颗值多少钱吗
You got a rough idea of its value?
目前的市场上
At current market,
20到25
200. 250.
万
Thousand?
对
Yes.
美金
Dollars?
没错
Yes.
你有多少颗
How many do you have?
朋友  这是个秘密
That, my friend, is a secret. Heh.
他妈的
Fuck me.
-请注意言词  -抱歉
- Language, please. - Sorry.
我们会让技术人员再检查一遍
Yeah, we'll get the tech people to look over it again.
好主意
That's a good idea.
坐下来喝一杯吧
Make a seat and drink, will you?
谢谢
Thanks.
我本应该得知这次袭击的
I should've known about this attack.
他们本应会告诉我
They should've told me.
你觉得他们不信任你
You don't think they trust you?
这只是更大计划中的一部分  对吗
This was part of something bigger, wasn't it?
获取北约基地的情报
To access information on NATO bases?
网络中枢是一切的关键
The hub is the key to everything.
晚上好  伙计们
Evening, guys,
你们好
Hey.
这是什么
What's that?
这是你在找的前女友的号码
It's the number of the ex-girlfriend you were looking for.
你好  特别探员
Special Agent.
你好  中士
Sergeant.
我们刚刚得到确认
So, it's just been confirmed--
麦坎娜的人在大使馆中拷贝了一个硬盘
MacKenna's people cloned a drive at the embassy.
他们要是破解了
Well, they decrypt it,
就会危害北约的运作
NATO's operationally compromised
整个欧洲都会暴露在
and the whole of Europe is exposed
朱海瑞的威胁下
to an attack by al-Zuhari.
当克隆硬盘被激活时
When it's activated,
它会发送一条特殊的可追踪信号
the cloned drive broadcasts a unique trackable signal.
我们在一小时前探测到了信号
We picked it up an hour ago.
在哪里
Where?
俄罗斯
Russia.
那是阿卡帝·乌尔诺夫的后花园
That's Arkady Ulyanov's backyard.
我们惨了  名列他黑名单第一位
We're fucked. We're on top of his shit list.